No man left behind
The Great War is a history, war, drama film directed by Steven Luke.
In November of 1918 as World War I was ending, a unit of American soldiers goes
behind enemy lines to find a lost platoon of African American soldiers.
Mary, played by Jordan McFadden.
General Pershing, played by Ron Perlman.
Nurse, played by Trinity Schuetzle.
Colonel Jack Morrison, played by Billy Zane.
Captain William Rivers, played by Bates Wilder.
O'Malley, played by Cody Fleury.
The Great War is a 2019 American war drama film written and directed
by Steven Luke and starring Bates Wilder, Hiram A.
Murray, Billy Zane and Ron Perlman.
The tone is emotional.